http://www.leohamel.com/terms-and-conditions

Login
Recently added item(s)
×
You have no items in your shopping cart.
SALES & SPECIALS
Find a huge selection, great prices, and personal service at Leo's!
Visit our Luxurious Showroom
1851 San Diego Ave. San Diego, CA 92110
Map & Directions
Custom Design
If you can dream it, we can make it.
Personal Shopper
If we don’t have it, we can find it for you.
Request a Personal Shopper
Our Boutique
Designer Fashion Consignments
Shop, Sell, Trade, Consign!
View All
Fair & friendly buyers who pay the best possible price at a location near you
Designer Fashion Consignments
Sell, Trade, Consign!
Our master jewelers & watchmaker have over 100 years of experience at the bench
Jewelry Repair
Perfection is our standard.
Restoration Services
Restore your jewelry or watch to like-new condition.
Watch Repair
Swiss factory trained technicians
Custom Design
If you can dream it, we can make it.
Terms
By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trademark law.
Use License
Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on Leo Hamel Fine Jewelers’ web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license, you may not:
modify or copy the materials;
use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);
attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on Leo Hamel Fine Jewelers’ web site;
remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or
transfer the materials to another person or “mirror” the materials on any other server.
This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by Leo Hamel Fine Jewelers at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.
Disclaimer
The materials on Leo Hamel Fine Jewelers’ web site are provided “as is.” Leo Hamel Fine Jewelers makes no warranties, expressed or implied, and hereby disclaims and negates all other warranties, including without limitation, implied warranties, or conditions of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or non-infringement of intellectual property or other violation of rights. Further, Leo Hamel Fine Jewelers does not warrant or make any representations concerning the accuracy, likely results, or reliability of the use of the materials on its Internet web site or otherwise relating to such materials or on any sites linked to this site.
Limitations
In no event shall Leo Hamel Fine Jewelers or its suppliers be liable for any damages (including, without limitation, damages for loss of data or profit, or due to business interruption,) arising out of the use or inability to use the materials on Leo Hamel Fine Jewelers’ Internet site, even if Leo Hamel Fine Jewelers or a Leo Hamel Fine Jewelers authorized representative has been notified orally or in writing of the possibility of such damage. Because some jurisdictions do not allow limitations on implied warranties, or limitations of liability for consequential or incidental damages, these limitations may not apply to you.
Revisions and Errata
The materials appearing on Leo Hamel Fine Jewelers’ web site could include technical, typographical, or photographic errors. Leo Hamel Fine Jewelers does not warrant that any of the materials on its web site are accurate, complete, or current. Leo Hamel Fine Jewelers may make changes to the materials contained on its web site at any time without notice. Leo Hamel Fine Jewelers does not, however, make any commitment to update the materials.
Links
Leo Hamel Fine Jewelers has not reviewed all of the sites linked to its Internet web site and is not responsible for the contents of any such linked site. The inclusion of any link does not imply endorsement by Leo Hamel Fine Jewelers of the site. Use of any such linked web site is at the user’s own risk.
Site Terms of Use Modifications
Leo Hamel Fine Jewelers may revise these terms of use for its web site at any time without notice. By using this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by the then current version of these Terms and Conditions of Use.
Governing Law
Any claim relating to Leo Hamel Fine Jewelers’ web site shall be governed by the laws of the State of California without regard to its conflict of law provisions.
General Terms and Conditions applicable to Use of a Web Site.
Privacy Policy
Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate, disclose, and make use of personal information. The following outlines our privacy policy.
Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected.
We will collect and use personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, including announcing events being held at our store, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law.
We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes.
We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned.
Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date.
We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.
We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.
We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.
